labcorp.com 2006-06-23

# LabCorp Privacy Statement

* * *

**LabCorp Privacy Statement**

Laboratory Corporation of America Holdings and its subsidiaries, including Laboratory Corporation of America (collectively "LabCorp"), is a national clinical laboratory that fully embraces genomic and molecular testing and has pioneered new diagnostic technologies. LabCorp is committed to protecting the privacy of every person who visits the LabCorp web site so that each person will feel free to gather information, make inquiries/comments, and/or perform bill payment functions on our site. As part of LabCorp's effort to protect the privacy of your personal information while visiting the LabCorp site, we created this privacy statement to inform you of the privacy standards used to ensure the security and confidentiality of your information. The following information details how LabCorp uses information that you provide to us via the LabCorp web site and answers commonly asked questions regarding the privacy of your individual information.

**What personal information does LabCorp collect?**

LabCorp does not ask you to provide personal health care information to us through our web site. We obtain personally identifying information about you only if you voluntarily choose to provide such information via e-mail comment to LabCorp. Our LabCorp e-mail correspondence link specifically requests that you not include personal medical information. The LabCorp bill payment link, which allows you to make electronic payments, requests that you provide personal financial data for the payment of invoices. Information from the bill payment link does not display or transmit any personal health care information about you or from your account.

**How does LabCorp protect the security of your information?**

Financial information and payment data, including credit card numbers, that you provide to us via the LabCorp Internet bill payment link is encrypted by using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology which employs a 128-bit encryption system. This information may be accessed only by LabCorp employees who maintain password and job-required access rights. Additionally, LabCorp maintains all personal patient data within the LabCorp information system (IS) firewalls that operate on separate LabCorp mainframes/servers. The general public may not access these mainframes/servers. 

**Cookies **

LabCorp tracks visitors to our web site by collecting data elements called "cookies." Cookies collected from LabCorp web site are used to: 1) identify which computer you are using, 2) assist in the navigation of the web site, and 3) remember computer settings. Cookies are not permanently maintained within our tracking system. You may prevent your computer from accepting cookies by modifying the properties on your web browser, however, stopping your computer from accepting cookies may limit your web browser's functionality on the LabCorp web site. 

**Internet Links**

As a convenience to our site visitors, the LabCorp web site contains links to a number of sites that may provide useful information. Links contained on the LabCorp web site which transfer you to a non-LabCorp site are not maintained by LabCorp and may contain different information and/or different privacy policies from those of our Company. You may review the privacy policies of these web sites and/or receive specific information regarding that site's privacy policies and procedures after leaving the LabCorp site. LabCorp is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of a non-LabCorp web site. LabCorp does not control, or have any input into, whether our business partners or Internet-linked sites use or accept cookies on their sites. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

LabCorp may alter or make changes to this privacy policy from time to time when developments occur and/or technology improvements are implemented. When changes are made, we will update our privacy policy and notices. Please review this page periodically to ensure that you are aware of any such updates.

**Your Consent**

By visiting and using the LabCorp web site, you consent to the terms outlined in this LabCorp Privacy Statement.

**Children's Access**

LabCorp is committed to the protection of children's privacy, security, and safety. Our web sites are created for an adult audience and are not designed or intended to attract children in any way. We do not knowingly solicit, collect, or accept any information from children on this web site.

**How to contact us**

LabCorp welcomes feedback and questions regarding our privacy policy. If you need further information or have questions regarding this privacy policy, please send an e-mail to: privacyofficer@labcorp.com 

Policy terms last updated: May 15, 2002
